

Contact me at

Kottayam, India

safalalikhan@gmail.com

safalalikhan

in safalalikhan

\(+918137888877

Education

Attended BTech in Information Technology,

Cochin University of Science And Technology, 2014-08 - 2018-05

Back-End Web Development,

Masai School, 2022-01 - 2022-09

Technical Skills

Java | SQL | Git

Soft Skills

Creativity | Problem-solving | Adaptability | Leadership | Time management

Interests

Travel | Football | Cycling

Accomplishments

- Volunteered in Mozilla Maker Party (Kochi)
- Mathematics Club Secretary (School Level)
- College Football Champion (University Level)

Safal Ali Khan

Back-end Developer

Personal Profile

Creative and diligent back-end developer with experience in more than 10 projects. Eager to work and constantly improve skills. Creative and always ready to solve any problems coming his way. Have experience running own startup and business for more than 4 years, managing different teams.

Work Experience

Organisation: Travethon Organisation: Zameer Agency

Position: Co-Founder **Position:** Manager

Duration: 2018-06 to 2020-03 **Duration:** 2020-03 to 2022-01

ROLES: Co-founded and ran the travel-**ROLES:** Managed sales and operations based startup in Kerala. Had managedfor the family business and have good different teams during the same.

experience interacting with clients.

Projects

Bobbi Brown Clone 🔘



Features

- · Dropdown Menus and Sliders
- · Signup and Login functionalities

Tech-Stack

JavaScript | CSS | HTML

Area of responsibility

Full Stack Developer

Web Application 🜎

Basic Application built completely on Java.

Features

- Efficient
- Interactive

Tech-Stack

Java | SQL | Git

Area of responsibility

· Back-End Developer